<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>EVA - a CRISPR story</title>
    <link>https://acrisprstory.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on EVA - a CRISPR story</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://acrisprstory.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://acrisprstory.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acrisprstory.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Puneet and Isabel’s research has achieved a clinical milestone using CRISPR technology to transplant a genetically modified pig liver into a human. This is just the beginning though and Isabel is on the cusp of perfecting CRISPR so that it can be used to modify human genome without any adverse side effects. The consequences could be unprecedented - a cure for many genetic disorders; but also potential genome editing of our future generations without their consent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://acrisprstory.com/festivals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acrisprstory.com/festivals/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://acrisprstory.com/stills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acrisprstory.com/stills/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://acrisprstory.com/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acrisprstory.com/support/</guid>
      <description>ihallo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://acrisprstory.com/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acrisprstory.com/team/</guid>
      <description>Puneet Bharill Born in India, just like most people around him, Puneet loved cinema. Following his dream of making his own film, he wrote his first screenplay in 2015 during his post doctoral research at the University hospital, Cologne where CRISPR was just being introduced as a technique in lab.
In 2018 he finally got the opportunity to direct this no-budget project which completed in February 2019.
Puneet has a PhD in Biochemistry and Molecular Biology from the University of Arkansas for Medical Sciences and is currently working as a Production Assistant in Cologne, Germany.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>